btips.net 2012-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Blogging Tips - SEO - Making Money

Privacy Policy

[Btips.net](http://btips.net/)  takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our website. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party. We don’t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

Comments/Message Boards

Btips.net  contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

Links

Btips.net   frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our website we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by [Btips.net](http://btips.net/)

Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

Contact Information

Use Contact Us page if you have any concerns or questions about this privacy policy
